Guide to the Andrew Dickson White papers, 1832-1919.
White, Andrew Dickson papers, 1832-1919
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 15, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    Letter. Addressed to Grove L. Johnson; two pages
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 15, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - F.B. Sanborn, October 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter to Prof. Wayland
  - Our Boston Literary Letter (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Commissioners of the District of Columbia, October 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Frederick White, October 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Horace White, October 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - S.A. Wilder, October 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Walter H. Page, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Julius D. Dreher, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - A.E. Keet, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - N., October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Robert Thiern, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Francis Wayland, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Frederick White, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Adolf Hepner, October 18, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Frank J. Enz, October 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Clifton R. Breckinridge, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - David J. Brewer, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - R.U. Johnson, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Charles H. Levermore, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Ellis H. Roberts, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - H.K. Carroll, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Theodore Stanton, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - R.R. Wallace, October 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Theodore Bacon, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Alfred Emerson, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - E., October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - S.P. Langley, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Ruth Mary White, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Frederick White, October 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - J.C. Hendrix, October 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, October 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    . "Golden Wedding of Mr. and Mrs. Gardiner Greene Hubbard"
  - George H. Lewis, October 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from/to M.A. Hanna
  - Henry Rumford Thompson, October 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Berlin Photographic Co., October 22, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Anna Parker P., October 22, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Goldwin Smith, October 22, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Goldwin Smith, October 22, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 22, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - C.B. Abbe, October 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, October 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - M.M. Dana, October 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - H.L. Nelson, October 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Frederick P., October 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Charles C. Beaman, October 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    Letter. The University Club in the City of New York
  - C.B. Abbe, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - H.B. Brown, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - James Parker Hall, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - R.U. Johnson, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - R.U. Johnson, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Undescribed, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Frederick White, October 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Louis Bedell Grant, October 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Richard O., October 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - W.A. Reynolds, October 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - H.E. Tutherly, October 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - John Henry Comstock, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - H.K. Carroll, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - E.E. Lull, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Charles H. Moss, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - F.B. Sanborn, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    Letter. Addressed to Jacob Bickler; two pages
  - Edwin C. Stewart, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Frederick White, October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - George M. Atwood, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Erastus Corning, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - A.E. Keet, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - George C. Sargent, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - William H. Ward, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    Letter. Addressed to J.H. Comstock
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Horace White, October 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Theodore Barth, October 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Eva A. B., October 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - E., October 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., October 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - E. L., October 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Andrew Dickson White, October 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - David J. Brewer, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - H.K. Carroll, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - J. Roger Lewis, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - N., October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Charles W.D. Parsons, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - George Van de Water, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - E.S. Plumb, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - George L. Burr, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - James Woolworth, October 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Ernest W. Huffcut, October 31, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - S.P. Langley, October 31, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - A.C. Moss, October 31, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Jacob Miller, October 31, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Horace White, October 31, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Myles R. Haddenden, October 31, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - A.E. Keet, October 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Julius D. Dreher, October 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    Letter. Roanoke College
  - Wayne MacVeagh, October 1896 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Pierre, November 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - E.H. Sellers, November 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - George Lincoln Burr, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - H.L. Nelson, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - A.E. Hutchins, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - A.H. Thompson, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - L.M. Outwater, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - F.G. Tiffany, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Frederick White, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - H.S. White, November 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - John W. Hoyt, November 3, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - E.O. Randall, November 3, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Undescribed, November 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - J. Fletcher Fullard, November 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Jacob Miller, November 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - E.H. Sellers, November 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - J.M. Hamman, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - James McKeen, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Joseph May, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - John Addison Porter, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Goldwin Smith, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - George R. Van de Water, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Frederick White, November 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - John W. Hoyt, November 6, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - A.E. Keet, November 6, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 6, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - E.S. Plumb, November 6, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Edward H. Randolph, November 6, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - James B. Angell, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - M. Clum, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - W.H. Colson, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - M.L. D'Ooge, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - J.C. Hendrix, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - John W. Hoyt, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - O.F. Williams, November 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Florence S. Boardman, November 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - L.K. Browne, November 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Andrew Newberry, November 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Frederick White, November 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler, November 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Donald Dey, November 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - W. Gannett Horder, November 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - F.A. Morey, November 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - W.E. Waters, November 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Clifford C. Whitmore, November 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - B.F. Burnham, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - O.E. Curtis, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - A.H. Fretageot, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Carrie M. Holls, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - A.E. Keet, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Jacob Miller, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Theodore T. Munger, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Daisy M. Reid, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - H. Ward, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Jno. Williams, November 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Charles R. Barth, November 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Frank S. B., November 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - J. Busche, November 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Ellis H. Roberts, November 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - C.A., November 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Florence S. Boardman, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - A.E. Keet, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Pastor C. Philit, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - John Addison Porter, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - J.G. Schurman, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - George R. Van de Water, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Frederick White, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Letter. Addressed to W. McKinley; two pages
  - H.S. Ballou, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Foster Coate, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - W.H. Colson, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Elizabeth P. Evans, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Undescribed, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Alfred Millard, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - N., November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - F.G. Tiffany, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - J.E. Travor, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - E.G. Allen, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - R.L. Burrows, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - E.P. Evans, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - A.E. Keet, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - R.C. McCormick, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Clara White Newberry, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Shoemaker, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Thomas R. Slicer, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Lucien A. Wait, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - W.H. Ward, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Strong White, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    Letter. White's nephew; two pages
  - Ernest Ingersol White, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Frederick White, November 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Albert Hamilton, November 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - A.E. Keet, November 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - E.S. Plumb, November 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 16, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - D. Appleton & Co., November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Jessie Cassidy, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - William McKinley, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - A.F. Matthews, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Jacob Miller, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Arthur C. Wakeley, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    Letter. Addressed to Clara White Newberry
  - Horace White, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Clinton Rogers Woodruff, November 17, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    Letter. National Civil-Service Reform League
  - Nicholas Murray Butler, November 18, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 18, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
    Letter. Addressed to J.J. Schurman; two pages
  - George M. Chadwick, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - E.T. Cox, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Ephraim Cutter, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - George Henry Fox, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Juliet L.P. Hill, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Ripley Hitchcock, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Jacob Miller, November 19, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Stephen S. Burt, November 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - M. Clum, November 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Undescribed, November 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Helen Magill White, November 20, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Undescribed, November 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth C. H., November 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - John Boyd Thacher, November 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Letter. Addressed to P. Schurman
  - Ruth Mary White, November 21, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - E.S. Plumb, November 22, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - C.W. Andrews, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - M. Clum, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - C.K. Cullen, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - W.W. Dedrick, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - James C. Egbert, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - H.C. Frick, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Ripley Hitchcock, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - F.F. Jordan, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - C.M. Holls, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Goldwin Smith, November 23, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - F. Sinclair Barbarin, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    Letter. The Corcoran Gallery of Art
  - J. Busche, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - George H. Story, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    Letter. Metropolitan Museum of Art
  - A. A., November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - E., November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - John D. Milliken, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - E.O. Randall, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - F.B. Sanborn, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Oscar S. Straus, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - John Boyd Thacher, November 24, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - John M. Beatty, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - George Tucker Bispham, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - William D. Collingwood, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - L.T. Chamberlain, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    Letter. Enclosed: "Appeal from Harpoot"
  - Ephraim Cutter, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - N., November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - John Boyd Thacher, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - C. Stevens Patterson, November 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    Letter. Union League House
  - Lucien A. Wait, November 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - James Edward Oliver, November 26, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    Memorial. "In Memory of James Edward Oliver"
  - Horace White, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Clifford C. Whitmore, November 25, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - H.B. Adams, November 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - P.A. Gibbons, November 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - A. Llamo, November 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - J.M. Whiton, November 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 27, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Gardiner G. Hubbard, November 28, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    Letter. Enclosed: letter from F.D. McGuire
  - H. Allen, November 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - E.P. Evans, November 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - E.E. Evans, November 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - C.M. Holls, November 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Frederick White, November 29, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Mary E. Arnold, November 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Lilliam W. Fay, November 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - William O. McDowell, November 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - E.S. Plumb, November 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - John Boyd Thacher, November 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - John W. Woodruff, November 30, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - The Literary Society, November 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - William H. Johnson, November 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Seth; William; John Low; Keener; Burgess, November 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Curry, November 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Andrew Dickson White, November 1896 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    Letter. Addressed to Frederick William Holls; six pages; first page missing
  - McKinley, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - W.R. Hearst, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Edward H. Kendall, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - M.Fay Peirce, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Charles Dudley Warner, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Frederick White, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - The Oneida Historical Society, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - The Oneida Historical Society, December 1, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    Dedication.
  - James M. Dalell, December 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Godfrey & Gilbert, December 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Sherman, December 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    Letter. Metropolitan Club
  - E.L. Nelson, December 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - George E. Priest, December 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Frederick White, December 2, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - George B. Syres, December 3, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - A.W. Bishop, December 3, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - James Julius Chambers, December 3, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Mary Olivia R., December 3, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - George A. Benham, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - J. Edwards Clarke, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Severo Mallet-Prevost, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Homer B. Sprague, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - W.E.D. Stokes, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - The Troy Daily Times, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Charles Dudley Warner, December 4, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Charles Coudert, December 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - J.C. Egbert, December 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - W.W. Dedrick, December 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - E.C., December 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - A.E. Keet, December 5, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - William P. Aiken, December 6, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - W.H. Colson, December 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Cox, Sons, Buckley & Co., December 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Mary Olivia R., December 7, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Justine Brewer, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Morton Dexter, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Carrie M. Holls, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Rob T. J., December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    Letter. First Baptist Church
  - Theodore T. Munger, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - C. Stevens Patterson, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    Letter. Addressed to William McKinley
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 8, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    Letter. Addressed to W.H. Sage; two pages
  - Brown, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Nicholas Murray Butler, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - J. Madison C., December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Driscoll Bros. & Co., December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - William Henry Sage, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Ripley Hitchcock, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - E.S. Plumb, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Albert Shaw, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Uhl, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Benjamin Ide Wheeler, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Robert H. Wiles, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Frederick White, December 9, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - C.K. Adams, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - George S. Batcheller, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - A.W. Bishop, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - H.B. Hyde, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - E.R. Maxson, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - W.H. Miller, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad Co., December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - P. Gibbon, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - William D. Collingwod (Box 77, Folder 26)
    Letter. Sheet torn
  - Frederic A. Morey, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    Letter. Addressed to Albert Shaw
  - Horace K. White, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Undescribed, December 10, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    List.
  - Farmers' Fertilizer Company, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Cyrus Adler, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Susanna Phelps Gage, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Frederic Harrison, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Katherine Hewett, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Undescribed, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - W.L. McKay, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - J.B. Starms, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Frederick White, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - B.L. Whitman, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Walter F. Willcox, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - W.J. Youmans, December 11, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Henry T. Allen, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Mary J. Field, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - M. Gilmour, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - J.J. Hagerman, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Ian E. Montgomery, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - F.B. Sanborn, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Julia Stanford, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - E.P. Evans, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - David J. Hill, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Andrew Dickson White, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Horace White, December 12, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - A.H. A., December 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Ripley Hitchcock, December 13, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Marcia S. Andrews, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Clifton R. Breckinridge, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - H. Emerson, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Carrie M. Holls, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Clara White Newberry, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - The Philadelphia Press, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    Telegram. Two pages
  - "Schurman to White, Book 5, p. 117", December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Studer Brothers, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)
    Letter. "The Birds of North of America"
  - Charles Dudley Warner, December 14, 1896 (Box 77, Folder 28)